[
  { "id": 1, "answer": "none", "question": "I have strong beliefs about what is right and wrong, good and bad." },
  { "id": 2, "answer": "none", "question": "I often act without considering the possible consequences." },
  { "id": 3, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to solve problems using a step-by-step approach." },
  { "id": 4, "answer": "none", "question": "I believe that formal procedures and policies restrict people." },
  { "id": 5, "answer": "none", "question": "I have a reputation for saying what I think, simply and directly." },
  { "id": 6, "answer": "none", "question": "I often find that actions based on feelings are as sound as those based on careful thought and analysis." },
  { "id": 7, "answer": "none", "question": "I like the sort of work where I have time for thorough preparation and implementation." },
  { "id": 8, "answer": "none", "question": "I regularly question people about their basic assumptions." },
  { "id": 9, "answer": "none", "question": "What matters most is whether something works in practice." },
  { "id": 10, "answer": "none", "question": "I actively seek out new experiences." },
  { "id": 11, "answer": "none", "question": "When I hear about a new idea or approach I immediately start working out how to apply it in practice." },
  { "id": 12, "answer": "none", "question": "I am keen on self-discipline such as watching my diet, taking regular exercise, sticking to a fixed routine, etc." },
  { "id": 13, "answer": "none", "question": "I take pride in doing a thorough job." },
  { "id": 14, "answer": "none", "question": "I get on best with logical, analytical people and less well with spontaneous, 'irrational' people." },
  { "id": 15, "answer": "none", "question": "I take care over the interpretation of data available to me and avoid jumping to conclusions." },
  { "id": 16, "answer": "none", "question": "I like to reach a decision carefully after weighing up many alternatives." },
  { "id": 17, "answer": "none", "question": "I'm attracted more to novel, unusual ideas than to practical ones." },
  { "id": 18, "answer": "none", "question": "I don't like disorganised things and prefer to fit things into a coherent pattern." },
  { "id": 19, "answer": "none", "question": "I accept and stick to laid down procedures and policies so long as I regard them as an efficient way of getting the job done." },
  { "id": 20, "answer": "none", "question": "I like to relate my actions to a general principle." },
  { "id": 21, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions I like to get straight to the point." },
  { "id": 22, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to have distant, rather formal relationships with people at work." },
  { "id": 23, "answer": "none", "question": "I thrive on the challenge of tackling something new and different." },
  { "id": 24, "answer": "none", "question": "I enjoy fun-loving, spontaneous people." },
  { "id": 25, "answer": "none", "question": "I pay meticulous attention to detail before coming to a conclusion." },
  { "id": 26, "answer": "none", "question": "I find it difficult to produce ideas on impulse." },
  { "id": 27, "answer": "none", "question": "I believe in coming to the point immediately." },
  { "id": 28, "answer": "none", "question": "I am careful not to jump to conclusions too quickly." },
  { "id": 29, "answer": "none", "question": "I prefer to have as many sources of information as possible - the more data to mull over the better." },
  { "id": 30, "answer": "none", "question": "Flippant people who don't take things seriously enough usually irritate me." },
  { "id": 31, "answer": "none", "question": "I listen to other people's point of view before putting my own forward." },
  { "id": 32, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to be open about how I'm feeling." },
  { "id": 33, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions I enjoy watching the manoeuvrings of the other participants." },
  { "id": 34, "answer": "none", "question": "I prefer to respond to events on a spontaneous, flexible basis rather than plan things out in advance." },
  { "id": 35, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to be attracted to techniques such as network analysis, flow charts, branching programmes, contingency planning, etc." },
  { "id": 36, "answer": "none", "question": "It worries me if I have to rush out a piece of work to meet a tight deadline." },
  { "id": 37, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to judge people's ideas on their practical merits." },
  { "id": 38, "answer": "none", "question": "Quiet, thoughtful people tend to make me feel uneasy." },
  { "id": 39, "answer": "none", "question": "I often get irritated by people who want to rush things." },
  { "id": 40, "answer": "none", "question": "It is more important to enjoy the present moment than to think about the past or future." },
  { "id": 41, "answer": "none", "question": "I think that decisions based on a thorough analysis of all the information are sounder than those based on intuition." },
  { "id": 42, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to be a perfectionist." },
  { "id": 43, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions I usually produce lots of spontaneous ideas." },
  { "id": 44, "answer": "none", "question": "In meetings I put forward practical realistic ideas." },
  { "id": 45, "answer": "none", "question": "More often than not, rules are there to be broken." },
  { "id": 46, "answer": "none", "question": "I prefer to stand back from a situation and consider all the perspectives." },
  { "id": 47, "answer": "none", "question": "I can often see inconsistencies and weaknesses in other people's arguments." },
  { "id": 48, "answer": "none", "question": "On balance I talk more than I listen." },
  { "id": 49, "answer": "none", "question": "I can often see better, more practical ways to get things done." },
  { "id": 50, "answer": "none", "question": "I think written reports should be short and to the point." },
  { "id": 51, "answer": "none", "question": "I believe that rational, logical thinking should win the day." },
  { "id": 52, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to discuss specific things with people rather than engaging in social discussion." },
  { "id": 53, "answer": "none", "question": "I like people who approach things realistically rather than theoretically." },
  { "id": 54, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions I get impatient with irrelevancies and digressions." },
  { "id": 55, "answer": "none", "question": "If I have a report to write I tend to produce lots of drafts before settling on the final version." },
  { "id": 56, "answer": "none", "question": "I am keen to try things out to see if they work in practice." },
  { "id": 57, "answer": "none", "question": "I am keen to reach answers via a logical approach." },
  { "id": 58, "answer": "none", "question": "I enjoy being the one that talks a lot." },
  { "id": 59, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions I often find I am the realist, keeping people to the point and avoiding wild speculations." },
  { "id": 60, "answer": "none", "question": "I like to ponder many alternatives before making up my mind." },
  { "id": 61, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions with people I often find I am the most dispassionate and objective." },
  { "id": 62, "answer": "none", "question": "In discussions I'm more likely to adopt a 'low profile' than to take the lead and do most of the talking." },
  { "id": 63, "answer": "none", "question": "I like to be able to relate current actions to a longer-term bigger picture." },
  { "id": 64, "answer": "none", "question": "When things go wrong I am happy to shrug it off and 'put it down to experience'." },
  { "id": 65, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to reject wild, spontaneous ideas as being impractical." },
  { "id": 66, "answer": "none", "question": "It's best to think carefully before taking action." },
  { "id": 67, "answer": "none", "question": "On balance I do the listening rather than the talking." },
  { "id": 68, "answer": "none", "question": "I tend to be tough on people who find it difficult to adopt a logical approach." },
  { "id": 69, "answer": "none", "question": "Most times I believe the end justifies the means." },
  { "id": 70, "answer": "none", "question": "I don't mind hurting people's feelings so long as the job gets done." },
  { "id": 71, "answer": "none", "question": "I find the formality of having specific objectives and plans stifling." },
  { "id": 72, "answer": "none", "question": "I'm usually one of the people who puts life into a party." },
  { "id": 73, "answer": "none", "question": "I do whatever is expedient to get the job done." },
  { "id": 74, "answer": "none", "question": "I quickly get bored with methodical, detailed work." },
  { "id": 75, "answer": "none", "question": "I am keen on exploring the basic assumptions, principles and theories underpinning things and events." },
  { "id": 76, "answer": "none", "question": "I'm always interested to find out what people think." },
  { "id": 77, "answer": "none", "question": "I like meetings to be run on methodical lines, sticking to laid down agenda, etc." },
  { "id": 78, "answer": "none", "question": "I steer clear of subjective or ambiguous topics." },
  { "id": 79, "answer": "none", "question": "I enjoy the drama and excitement of a crisis situation." },
  { "id": 80, "answer": "none", "question": "People often find me insensitive to their feelings." }
]